{
    "subject": "resource/Prior_Scientific",
    "predicate": "property/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.prior.com/",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of Prior Scientific is http://www.prior.com/",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9398306608200073,
            "question": "Give the website address for Prior Scientific."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9267423152923584,
            "question": "What is the URL of the Prior Scientific homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9069644808769226,
            "question": "What is the web address of Prior Scientific's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8588054180145264,
            "question": "What website address belongs to Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229626417160034,
            "question": "If you want to visit Prior Scientific's website, what URL should you enter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8163281679153442,
            "question": "What is the URL of Prior Scientific's main page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8063542246818542,
            "question": "How do you access the website for Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7728203535079956,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Prior Scientific online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7601355314254761,
            "question": "What is the online location of Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7448251843452454,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Prior Scientific on the internet?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of Prior Scientific is http://www.prior.com/",
            "html": "dbpedia_6736_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the online location of Prior Scientific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6736_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find information about Prior Scientific online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6736_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do you access the website for Prior Scientific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6736_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_158.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6736_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions the website `http://www.prior.com` for Prior Scientific Instruments, which supports that the provided homepage URL is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no explicit statement in the context information that specifies the homepage of Prior Scientific as http://www.prior.com/. Instead, it only provides the website address (www.prior-scientific.co.uk) for their UK company profile page.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states the website address as www.prior.com multiple times, indicating its accuracy.  Furthermore, no conflicting information is presented to suggest otherwise.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The website of Prior Scientific mentioned in context information 2 is http://www.prior-scientific.co.uk, not http://www.prior.com.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context provides the website as \"www.prior.com\", not \"http://www.prior-scientific.co.uk\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}